Narrator: 1
M: I feel as though I’ve been with this company forever; in fact, by 2035,
I’ll have been working here for 25 years.
Narrator: 2
F: I never knew he’d worked as a teacher when he was younger.
I thought he’d always been in the music business.
Narrator: 3
M: I was working as a waiter in a cocktail bar when I met my partner.
Narrator: 4
F: Both my kids are working this summer because they want to earn some money to go travelling in September.
Narrator: 5
F: Have you really been working in the garden all morning?
It doesn’t look as though you’ve done very much!
Narrator: 6
F: Ann is a world-class make-up artist and has worked with over two hundred Hollywood stars.
Narrator: 7
M: Most of the Ford employees had been working on the new model for over six months
when the news of the factory closure was announced.
Narrator: 8
M: Will you be working from home at all next week, or will you be in the office every day?